(Howard(on phone):)Okay, Ma.
(Howard(on phone):)Say hi to Aunt Gladys.
(Howard(on phone):)Yeah, I love you,
too.
(Howard(on phone):)Bye.
(Bernadette:)Your mom having fun in Florida?
(Howard:)Mmm, she loves it.
(Howard:)She finally found a place
where everyone talks about
(Howard:)how sweaty they are.
(Howard:)Anyway, she wants us
to go to the house
(Howard:)and check in on Stuart
because he might be "lonely."
(Bernadette:)She's just being nice.
(Howard:)Well, I'm her son, how come
she doesn't send someone
(Howard:)to check on me if I'm lonely?
(Bernadette:)Because you have a wife.
(Howard:)Yeah, well, sometimes
you work late.
(Bernadette:)I know you don't like
Stuart being in the house,
(Bernadette:)but the store's
about to reopen,
(Bernadette:)I'm sure he'll get
back on his feet.
(Howard:)That would be great.
(Howard:)I'd love for things between me
and Mom to get back to normal.
(Bernadette:)Well, normal's a
strong word, but sure.
(Barry:)Hey.
Hello.
(Penny:)You okay?
(Sheldon:)If I was okay,
I would've said "hello"